b2k and the Special Olympics team and
the athletes and of course to all of our
friends from the media this is probably
the most fun and exciting venue that
we've done anything with which is
usually in hotels and stuff so great job
rush I'm thinking this and and all the
fun games are going to have a bit later
on so well
just let me start off by just a few
remarks I want to say how excited we are
to be working with the Special Olympics
team as FWD launches a new three-year
community care program across Asia in
fact empowering people with disability
at FWD we all care a great deal about
giving back we want to help bleed
positive change by encouraging social
inclusion and advocating equal
opportunities for people with
disabilities we will at FWD be
partnering with a number of
organizations in Asia to help us achieve
this goal but today we specifically
celebrate the partnership with Special
Olympics to kick this all off together
and hear a little bit more about this
one when she talks us through the
programs but we will be launching the
new unified schools and athlete
leadership programs for young people
with intellectual disabilities here in
the Philippines and similar activities
to this are going on across Asia in the
other markets in which FWD operates
I was told we have a lot to get through
and some of the stuff that we're gonna
be hearing we'll be hearing from later
on in the program is a lot more
interesting than listening to me as well
as I believe there is some sporting
activities were unsure the competitive
do
I'm not sure I saw already the
competitive juices of everybody of
flowing fully so I may keep my remarks
short so that you can hear from the
people that really matter they'll be
listening to Ross walk you through the
program k is going to say a few words in
a minute but most of all I think you're
going to be hearing from a couple of
Anthony to truly are inspirational
people I've had the privilege to listen
to them speak before and every time I do
I'm convert so we now further adieu let
me wrap this up by just simply saying
Thank You Kate Thank You Special
Olympics and giving us the opportunity
to make a difference
[Music]